<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>os.skillfish.Tuner</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>SkillFishOS Tuner</name>
  <summary>Overclock, undervolt and tune the AMD BC-250 without a terminal</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Overclock, undervolt e tuning della AMD BC-250 senza terminale</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Overclocking, undervolting i tuning AMD BC-250 bez terminala</summary>
  <description>
    <p>The control centre for the AMD BC-250: overclock and undervolt the CPU, drive the GPU safe-point governor, control the fan, resize the shared VRAM, and manage Compute Units live — a grid of CU squares (24/32/40 presets, no reboot) with a CU health test for the silicon lottery.</p>
    <p>Four ready presets (Stock, Performance, Turbo, Crazy), benchmark-and-rollback testing that applies a setting, stresses it and reverts if unstable, and a pop-up live monitor during any test. Multi-language (IT/EN/PL); privileged actions go through a single authenticated helper.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il centro di controllo della AMD BC-250: overclock e undervolt della CPU, governor GPU al safe-point, controllo ventola, ridimensionamento della VRAM condivisa e gestione live delle Compute Unit — una griglia di quadratini CU (preset 24/32/40, senza riavvio) con un test di salute CU per la lotteria del silicio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Quattro preset pronti (Stock, Performance, Turbo, Crazy), test con benchmark-e-rollback che applica un'impostazione, la stressa e la ripristina se instabile, e un monitor live durante ogni test. Multilingua (IT/EN/PL); le azioni privilegiate passano da un singolo helper autenticato.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Centrum sterowania dla AMD BC-250: overclocking i undervolting CPU, sterowanie governorem GPU w bezpiecznym punkcie pracy, kontrola wentylatora, zmiana rozmiaru współdzielonego VRAM oraz zarządzanie Compute Units na żywo — siatka kwadratów CU (presety 24/32/40, bez restartu) z testem kondycji CU dla loterii krzemowej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Cztery gotowe presety (Stock, Performance, Turbo, Crazy), testowanie benchmark-i-rollback, które stosuje ustawienie, obciąża je testem i cofa, jeśli jest niestabilne, oraz podręczny monitor na żywo podczas każdego testu. Wielojęzyczny (IT/EN/PL); uprzywilejowane operacje przechodzą przez jeden uwierzytelniony helper.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">os.skillfish.Tuner.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">skillfishos</icon>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
    <category>Settings</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>overclock</keyword>
    <keyword>undervolt</keyword>
    <keyword>tuner</keyword>
    <keyword>fan</keyword>
    <keyword>bc-250</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <url type="homepage">https://skillfishos.com</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/MTSistemi/SkillFishOS/issues</url>
  <developer id="com.skillfishos"><name>SkillFishOS</name></developer>
  <pkgname>skillfish-tuner</pkgname>
  <provides><binary>skillfish-tuner</binary></provides>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Tuner main window</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Finestra principale del Tuner</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Główne okno Tunera</caption>
      <image type="source">file:///usr/share/skillfish/screenshots/tuner.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Live Compute Unit grid</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Griglia Compute Unit live</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Siatka Compute Unit na żywo</caption>
      <image type="source">file:///usr/share/skillfish/screenshots/tuner-full.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>CU health test</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Test di salute delle CU</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Test kondycji CU</caption>
      <image type="source">file:///usr/share/skillfish/screenshots/cu-test.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="26.06.7" date="2026-06-10">
      <description><p>Find-my-max wizards for CPU and GPU with per-step benchmark-and-rollback; crash-safe testing; Turbo/Crazy presets capped at the validated 2200 MHz; extreme-preset warning; anonymous silicon-lottery sharing.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="26.06.6" date="2026-06-10">
      <description><p>GPU governor Balanced/Performance mode toggle (+11% FPS in GPU-bound loads) and the safe multi-point voltage curve.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="26.06.3" date="2026-06-08"/>
  </releases>
</component>
