<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>os.skillfish.monitor</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>SkillFishOS Monitor</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">SkillFishOS Monitor</name>
  <summary>Live temperature, frequency, voltage and fan charts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Grafici live di temperatura, frequenza, voltaggio e ventola</summary>
  <description>
    <p>A standalone live dashboard for the AMD BC-250: real-time line charts of CPU and GPU temperature, clock frequency, GPU voltage and fan speed, read straight from the hardware sensors.</p>
    <p>Sensor sampling runs on a background thread so the interface stays smooth, and the refresh interval is adjustable. Part of the native SkillFishOS app suite.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Un cruscotto live indipendente per l'AMD BC-250: grafici in tempo reale di temperatura CPU e GPU, frequenza di clock, voltaggio GPU e velocità della ventola, letti direttamente dai sensori hardware.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Il campionamento dei sensori gira su un thread dedicato così l'interfaccia resta fluida, e l'intervallo di aggiornamento è regolabile. Fa parte della suite di app native di SkillFishOS.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">os.skillfish.monitor.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">skillfishos</icon>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
    <category>Monitor</category>
  </categories>
  <keywords>
    <keyword>monitor</keyword>
    <keyword>sensors</keyword>
    <keyword>temperature</keyword>
    <keyword>fan</keyword>
  </keywords>
  <url type="homepage">https://skillfishos.com</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/MTSistemi/SkillFishOS/issues</url>
  <developer id="com.skillfishos">
    <name>SkillFishOS</name>
  </developer>
  <pkgname>skillfish-monitor</pkgname>
  <provides>
    <binary>skillfish-monitor</binary>
  </provides>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Live temperature, frequency, voltage and fan charts</caption>
      <image type="source">file:///usr/share/skillfish/screenshots/monitor.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <releases>
    <release version="26.06.6" date="2026-06-10">
      <description>
        <p>Monitor v2: added power (W) and CPU/GPU load charts (six panels total); refresh now selectable down to 0.5 s. Recordings are saved as .sfmon files (CSV-backed) and can be re-opened in the Monitor as a benchmark analyzer with a time scrubber to inspect the whole run second by second.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="26.06.5" date="2026-06-10">
      <description><p>REC button: record telemetry to CSV with a min/avg/max summary at the end of the session.</p></description>
    </release>
    <release version="26.06.3" date="2026-06-08"/>
  </releases>
</component>
